♪I'll go with you to see your favorite flower in spring♪
♪سأذهب معك لرؤية زهرتك ​​المفضلة في الربيع♪
♪I'll treat you to your favorite ice cream in summer♪
♪ سأقدم لك الآيس كريم المفضل لديك في الصيف ♪
♪I'll be with you in the rain when you're sad in autumn♪
♪ سأكون معك تحت المطر عندما تكون حزيناً في الخريف ♪
♪I'll build a snowman for you in winter♪
♪ سأبني لك رجل ثلج في الشتاء ♪
♪Only you can have my romance♪
♪ أنت فقط من تستطيع الحصول على رومانسيتي ♪
♪Everyone else is secondary♪
♪ الجميع ثانوي ♪
♪I like your every smile and frown♪
♪ أحب كل ابتسامتك وعبوسك ♪
♪Please let me hold your hand♪
♪ من فضلك دعني أمسك يدك ♪
♪I want to take you to watch the stars♪
♪أريد أن آخذك لمشاهدة النجوم♪
♪Please♪
♪من فضلك♪
♪Let me take care of you♪
♪ دعني أعتني بك ♪
♪Please let me hold your hand♪
♪ من فضلك دعني أمسك يدك ♪
♪When it's cold, hide in my arms♪
♪ عندما يكون الجو بارداً، إختبئ بين ذراعي ♪
♪Drive all your sadness♪
♪ تخلص من كل حزنك ♪
♪Completely away♪
♪بعيد تمامًا♪
=Falling In Love With Me= =Episode 7=
=الوقوع في حبي= =الحلقة 7=
Have we
هل نحن؟
met somewhere before?
اجتمع في مكان ما من قبل؟
Tong Yuxin.
تونغ يوكسين.
That's right.
صحيح.
You are Tong Yuxin,
أنت تونغ يوكسين،
the biggest fraud as a singer.
أكبر عملية احتيال كمغنية.
I spent so much on your songs and related items.
لقد أنفقت الكثير على أغانيك والأشياء ذات الصلة.
Refund my money.
برد أموالي.
Why am I a fraud?
لماذا أنا محتال؟
I'm profligate
أنا مسرف
or I broke the law?
أو أنني خرقت القانون؟
You seem to ruin yourself in a new way.
يبدو أنك تدمر نفسك بطريقة جديدة.
The song is the same,
الأغنية هي نفسها،
but it sounds completely different.
ولكن يبدو مختلفا تماما.
I sing badly,
أغني بشكل سيء
but I always sing badly.
لكنني دائما أغني بشكل سيء.
Just my fans don't like me anymore,
فقط جماهيري لم تعد تحبني بعد الآن
so I'm wrong?
لذلك أنا مخطئ؟
You heartless fans.
أيها المشجعين بلا قلب.
It seems to make a bit of sense.
يبدو أن الأمر منطقي بعض الشيء.
When you liked me,
عندما أعجبت بي،
you thought I was perfect.
اعتقدت أنني كنت مثاليا.
When you don't,
عندما لا تفعل ذلك،
you defame me now.
أنت تشوه سمعتي الآن.
No one can be more ruthless than you guys.
لا يمكن لأحد أن يكون أكثر قسوة منكم يا رفاق.
And you want me to refund your money.
وتريد مني أن أرد أموالك.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I am wrong.
أنا مخطئ.
Why are you wrong?
لماذا أنت مخطئ؟
I shouldn't
لا ينبغي لي
have been disloyal as a fan.
لقد كانوا غير مخلصين كمشجعين.
I promise to remain your fan, okay?
أعدك أن أبقى من معجبيك، حسنًا؟
Then
ثم
promise me one thing.
وعدني بشيء واحد.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
Leave it to me.
اتركه لي.
Mr. Tang, thank you so much.
السيد تانغ، شكرا جزيلا لك.
I will pay you back soon.
سأدفع لك قريبا.
Why did you borrow money from Tong Yuxin?
لماذا اقترضت المال من تونغ يوشين؟
We were high school classmates.
كنا زملاء الدراسة في المدرسة الثانوية.
We used to be close.
لقد اعتدنا أن نكون قريبين.
Sorry. I said you are my boyfriend.
آسف.  قلت أنك صديقي.
I just wanted to upset her.
أردت فقط أن أزعجها.
But I didn't mean that.
لكنني لم أقصد ذلك.
You said it two years ago.
انت قلتها قبل سنتين
Don't repeat it.
لا تكرر ذلك.
Mr. Tang.
السيد.  تانغ.
I know you're kind.
أعلم أنك لطيف.
But you just look cold.
لكنك تبدو باردًا فحسب.
You're a nice person.
أنت شخص لطيف.
You always help me
أنت دائما تساعدني
when I ask you.
عندما أسألك.
You're so nice.
أنت لطيف جدا.
No need for flattery.
لا حاجة للإطراء.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Are you in trouble?
هل انت في مشكلة؟
No.
لا.
I've made a fortune as an influencer.
لقد صنعت ثروة كمؤثر.
I've bought a villa recently
لقد اشتريت فيلا مؤخرا
and I don't have enough cash.
وليس لدي ما يكفي من النقود.
The rest of the money is still in the bank
أما بقية الأموال فلا تزال في البنك
for interest.
من أجل الفائدة.
Your career can't last long.
حياتك المهنية لا يمكن أن تستمر طويلا.
Are you really not going to continue your studies
هل حقا لن تستمر في دراستك؟
and be a singer?
وتكون مغنية؟
I haven't sung for two years.
لم أغني منذ عامين.
I've forgotten how to sing.
لقد نسيت كيف أغني.
Mr. Tang, eat this.
سيد تانغ، تناول هذا.
I'm full.
انا ممتلئ.
I'll transfer
سأنقل
the money to you.
المال لك.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Mr. Tang.
السيد.  تانغ.
Are you sure the test paper of your brother is on the computer?
هل أنت متأكد من أن ورقة الاختبار الخاصة بأخيك موجودة على الكمبيوتر؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
The password?
كلمة السر؟
It's someone's birthday.
إنه عيد ميلاد شخص ما.
His girlfriend's birthday?
عيد ميلاد صديقته؟
Liszt.
ليزت.
His girlfriend has surname Li?
صديقته لها لقب لي؟
A great pianist and composer.
عازف البيانو والملحن العظيم.
My cousin's idol.
المعبود ابن عمي.
Are you illiterate?
هل أنت أمي؟
That Liszt.
تلك ليزت.
You scared me.
لقد أخفتني.
How can he have a girlfriend?
كيف يمكن أن يكون لديه صديقة؟
His mind is full of music.
عقله مليء بالموسيقى.
Whoever wants to be his girlfriend
من يريد أن تكون صديقته
has to pass his test first.
يجب أن يجتاز اختباره أولاً.
You and he...
أنت وهو...
No.
لا.
Who wants to be his girlfriend?
من يريد أن تكون صديقته؟
Go watch the door.
اذهب وراقب الباب.
Go.
يذهب.
Be fast.
كن سريعا.
He will be back soon.
وسوف يعود قريبا.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Yutong, you're back.
يوتونغ، لقد عدت.
Yutong, did you go to eat?
يوتونغ، هل ذهبت لتناول الطعام؟
Where did you go to eat?
أين ذهبت لتناول الطعام؟
Why didn't you tell me?
لماذا لم تخبرني؟
I'm so hungry.
أنا جائع جدا.
Did you go for a drink?
هل ذهبت لتناول مشروب؟
What did you drink?
ماذا شربت؟
Wine or Baijiu...
النبيذ أو بايجيو...
This wall is so white.
هذا الجدار أبيض للغاية.
Yutong, you can't take it off.
يوتونغ، لا يمكنك خلعه.
Why?
لماذا؟
I'll take a bath.
سوف آخذ حماما.
I mean well.
أعني جيدا.
You may regret it.
قد تندم عليه.
Go out.
الخروج.
Stop it.
توقف عن ذلك.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
- It was him. - It was her.
- لقد كان هو.  - لقد كانت هي.
Didn't you say you'd be my fan forever?
ألم تقل أنك ستظل معجبًا بي إلى الأبد؟
But he's my only cousin.
لكنه ابن عمي الوحيد.
But you...
لكنك...
No more whispering.
لا مزيد من الهمس.
When did you get so acquainted?
متى تعرفت على هذا النحو؟
Tong Yuxin,
تونغ يوكسين,
given your act of stealing test papers,
بالنظر إلى قيامك بسرقة أوراق الاختبار،
I'll redraft the test
سأعيد صياغة الاختبار
and double the difficulty.
ومضاعفة الصعوبة.
What?
ماذا؟
As for Liang Tete,
أما بالنسبة ليانج تيتي،
since you care so much about her,
وبما أنك تهتم بها كثيراً
you can take the test too.
يمكنك إجراء الاختبار أيضًا.
If you fail,
إذا كنت لا،
pack up and leave immediately.
احزم أمتعتك واترك على الفور.
Please don't.
من فضلك لا تفعل ذلك.
There are only three days left.
لم يتبق سوى ثلاثة أيام.
You guys study well.
يا رفاق تدرسون جيدا.
Why didn't you
لماذا لم تفعل ذلك
stop him?
أوقفوه؟
It's your own business.
إنه عملك الخاص.
Why should I care?
لماذا يجب أن أهتم؟
It's you.
انه انت.
Wasn't it easy?
ألم يكن الأمر سهلا؟
You blame me
انت تلومني
for what you said?
لماذا قلت؟
I said the wrong thing?
قلت الشيء الخطأ؟
(Here's a bonus clip.)
(إليك مقطع إضافي.)
=Falling In Love With Me=
=الوقوع في الحب معي=
You don't need
لا تحتاج
to see me out.
لرؤيتي خارجا.
I'm just gonna throw trash.
أنا فقط سأرمي القمامة.
Well,
حسنًا،
what is your relationship with Lin Xiaoqing?
ما هي علاقتك مع لين شياو تشينغ؟
She's my junior.
انها صغاري.
I once liked her,
لقد أحببتها ذات مرة،
but she rejected me.
لكنها رفضتني.
What about now?
ماذا عن الان؟
Why do you care?
لماذا تهتم؟
We're friends. Just tell me.
نحن اصدقاء.  فقط أخبرني.
Stop being so stingy. Just tell me.
توقف عن كونك بخيلًا جدًا.  فقط أخبرني.
Tang Yutong,
تانغ يوتونغ,
don't be tight-lipped.
لا تكن ضيق الشفاه.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
♪Neither love nor hate can describe our relationship now♪
♪ لا الحب ولا الكراهية يمكنهما وصف علاقتنا الآن ♪
♪Being friends will only make each other awkward♪
♪ لن يؤدي كوننا أصدقاء إلا إلى جعل بعضنا البعض محرجين ♪
♪In the few weeks after breaking up♪
♪ في الأسابيع القليلة بعد الانفصال ♪
♪I restrain myself from missing you♪
♪ أنا أمنع نفسي من أن أفتقدك ♪
♪Like a chronic disease, it comes and goes♪
♪ مثل المرض المزمن، يأتي ويذهب ♪
♪Maybe I'm to blame for loving too deeply♪
♪ ربما أنا الملام على الحب العميق ♪
♪Will time heal the heartbreak♪
♪ هل الزمن سيشفي حسرة القلب ♪
♪Or will it make it more painful♪
♪ أم أنه سيجعل الأمر أكثر إيلاما ♪
♪Missing you is an incurable disease♪
♪ اشتياقك داء لا شفاء منه ♪
♪Yet now I think of you again♪
♪ والآن أفكر فيك مرة أخرى ♪
♪Neither love nor hate can describe our relationship now♪
♪ لا الحب ولا الكراهية يمكنهما وصف علاقتنا الآن ♪
♪Being friends will only make each other awkward♪
♪ لن يؤدي كوننا أصدقاء إلا إلى جعل بعضنا البعض محرجين ♪
♪I am not afraid of lonely nights♪
♪أنا لا أخاف من الليالي المنعزلة♪
♪Everyone knows it is a lie♪
♪ الجميع يعلم أنها كذبة ♪
♪I don't want to bear the pain of missing again♪
♪ لا أريد أن أتحمل ألم الافتقاد مرة أخرى ♪
♪Can you please let me go♪
♪هل يمكنك أن تسمح لي بالذهاب ♪
♪The carriage of time won't stop♪
♪ لن تتوقف عربة الزمن ♪
♪I'm sorry. I can't be the person you're with for the rest of your life♪
♪ أنا آسف.  لا أستطيع أن أكون الشخص الذي أنت معه لبقية حياتك ♪